A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 9, Accession 2019:003 FA1717
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 9, Accession 2019:003
1968-2018
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation
FA1717
17.16 Cubic Feet 39 letter-size document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Biographical / Historical
The Henry Luce Foundation was established by Henry R. Luce in 1936. As a New York-based nonprofit organization, the Luce Foundation awards grants in American Art, Asian studies, Higher Education, Theology, and supports the Clare Boothe Luce Program for women in science, mathematics, and engineering.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Henry Luce Foundation in 2019.
Scope and Contents
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 9) consists primarily of grant and professorship files. There is also a substantial amount of material regarding the United States-China Cooperative Research program.
Arrangement
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 9) are arranged as follows:
Series 1: Project Files, 1996-2018
Series 2: Professorship Files, 1968-2018
Series 3: United States-China Cooperative Research Program, 1988-2010
Religions; International relations; United States -- Relations -- China; Art, American; Research grants -- Asia, Southeastern; Education, Higher; Environmental sciences; Theology -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Refugees -- United States
- Project Files, 1996-2018; 1
  - American Studies Association - Southeast Asian Scholars Participation at the Annual Meeting, 2010-2018 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arts Midwest - "Modern Spirit: The Art of George Morrison" Exhibition and Catalog, 2011-2015 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Asia Foundation - North Korea Dialogue and Exchange Program, 2005-2018 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Asian Art Museum - San Francisco Asian Art Forum for Museum Directors, 2014-2016 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ASIANetwork - Asian Art in the Undergraduate Curriculum, 2004-2016 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - ASIANetwork - Post-Doctoral Teaching Fellowship Program, 2009-2018 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Aspen Institute - Program to Inform Members of Congress about International Issues, 2009-2015 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Aspen Institute - Program to Inform Members of Congress about International Issues, 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 11-13)
  - Aspen Institute - Council of Women World Leaders, 2009-2018 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Aspen Institute - Aspen China Trialogue - Global Governance: Challenges and Expectations Conference, 2010-2018 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art - Reinterpret and Install the American Art Collection, 2007-2015 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Battery Dance Company - Dancing to Connect: US-China Project, 2010-2018 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Romare Bearden Foundation - Catalog and Preserve the Archives, 2013-2015 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Brooklyn Museum - "Strokes of Brilliance: John Sargent Watercolors" Exhibition, 2011-2015 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bureau for International Reporting - Religion and International Affairs Reporting (Renewal), 2013-2015 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - United States-China Policy Dialogue Project on Advancing Climate Cooperation, 2010-2015 (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
  - Center for Lao Studies - Organizational and Programming Capacity, 2010-2018 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Center for Lao Studies - Organizational and Programming Capacity - First International Conference on Lao Studies, Northern Illinois University, 2005 May 20-22 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Center on Law and Security, New York University School of Law - Presidential Powers: An American Debate Conference, 2006-2018 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Centurion Ministries - Advocacy on Behalf of Wrongly Convicted Prisoners, 2004-2018 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - F.Y. Chang Foundation, US-China Education Trust - International Conference Marking the 10th Anniversary of the American Studies Network, 2013-2015 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - China Education Initiative - US-China Teaching Fellows Program, 2010-2012 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Church of Our Lady of the Rosary and St. Elizabeth Seaton Shrine - Preservation of the 1793 James Watson House, 2007-2018 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - College of Charleston - "Forces of Nature" Exhibition a Multi-Institution Collaboration for Japanese Artists, 2006-2018 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - College of William and Mary - Internationalization of United States Education in the 21st Century Research and Conference, 2013-2015 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - College of Wooster - Environmental Analysis and Action Program, 2004-2015 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - College of Wooster - Severence Chemistry Building, 1998-2018 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Columbia University - Center for Democracy, Toleration, and Religion, 2009-2015 (Box 5, Folder 33-35)
  - Concordia University - Center for Hmong Studies, 2005-2018 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Connecticut Historical Society Museum - Catalog Software Program, 2004-2018 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Council for a Community of Democracies - Advance Worldwide Democratic Governance, 2004-2018 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Council of Independent Colleges - Leadership Development Programs, 2011-2015 (Box 6, Folder 39-41)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - China's Growing Diplomatic, Economic, and Security Presence, 2005-2018 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - East-West Center - Asia Matters for America, 2009-2015 (Box 7, Folder 43-45)
  - Exit Art - Transfer Archive to Fales Library, New York University, 2012-2015 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Farnsworth Art Museum - "From Mt. Lebanon to the World: The Shakers" Exhibition and Catalog, 2012-2015 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - The Five Project, Inc. - Training and Resource Development for Individuals with Disabilities in China, 2010-2018 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - FJC - New York Youth Funders Network, 2006-2018 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Fowler Museum - "Textiles of Timor, Island in the Woven Sea" Exhibition and Publication, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt Institute - "Freedom from Fear: FDR, Commander in Chief" Exhibition, 2005-2018 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Freer Gallery of Art and Arthur M. Sackler Gallery, Smithsonian Institution - Southeast Asia Kiln Site Excavation Training Workshop, 2012-2015 (Box 8, Folder 52-53)
  - Garden School - Suzanne W. Newman Grant, 2007-2017 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Garden School - Suzanne W. Newman Grant, 2010-2017 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Graduate Center, City University of New York - New York Art Worlds: Historical and Contemporary Perspectives Symposium, 2006-2010 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Greater Minneapolis Council of Churches - Leadership Development Program for Ex-Offenders, 2005-2018 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Florence Griswold Museum - Valerie Hunt Evans Study Center, 2006-2018 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Haverford School - Chinese Language Program, 2008-2018 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Herstory Writers Workshop, Inc. - General Support, 2010-2018 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Hiram College - Garfield Institute for Public Leadership's 2008-2009 Seminar Series, 2008-2018 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Huntington Library - Reinstall and Publis the American Art Collection, 2014-2015 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Hyde Collection - "Modern Nature: Georgia O'Keeffe and Lake George" Exhibition and Catalog, 2012-2015 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Independent Journalism Foundation - Burma Journalism Training Program, 2010-2015 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - International Crisis Group - Religion in Conflict and Instability in Yemen, Indonesia, Nigeria, and Somalia, 2010-2015 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - International Rescue Committee - Resettlement of Refugees in the United States, 2008-2018 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies - For Myanmar: The Dynamics of Positive Change Conference and Manuscript, 2013-2015 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Joslyn Art Museum - Reinstall the American Art Collection, 2011-2013 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - La Compagnia de Colombari - "Laude in Urbis" Production, New York City, 2005-2018 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - La Compagnia de Colombari - "Strangers and Other Angels" Production, New York City, 2009-2018 (Box 10, Frame 70)
  - LaGuardia Community College - World Pathways Heritage Language Program (First Cohort), 2013-2015 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - LaGuardia Community College - World Pathways Heritage Language Program (Second Cohort), 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 72-73)
  - Link Media - Link TV News, Cultural and Current Affairs Programming on East and Southeast Asia, 2011-2012 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art - "Chinese Paintings from Japanese Collections" Exhibition, 2013-2015 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Lucian Pye Graduate Fellowship, 2008-2018 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - McGill University - A New Historical Archaeology: Pre-Imperial and Imperial China, 2008-2018 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Memphis Brooks Museum of Art - "Marisol: Sculpture and Works on Paper" Exhibition and Catalog, 2010-2015 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - "The American West in Bronze, 1850-1925" Exhibition and Catalog, 2012-2015 (Box 11, Folder 79-80)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - "Lost Kingdoms of Early Southeast Asia, 5th to 8th Century" Exhibition and Catalog, 2013-2015 (Box 11, Folder 81-82)
  - Minnesota Public Radio/American Public Media - Asia Coverage on Marketplace, 2012-2015 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Morris Educational Foundation - Michelle Douenias Middle School Art Grant, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Museum of Art Fort Lauderdale - "William Glackens" Exhibition and Catalog, 2012-2015 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Museum of Modern Art - "Robert Gober" Exhibition and Catalog, 2013-2015 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - National Academy of Sciences - Gender Difference at Critical Transitions in the Careers of Science, Engineering, and Mathematics Faculty CWSEM Report, 2010-2015 (Box 12, Folder 87-88)
  - National Bureau of Asian Research - Reemergence of Burma/Myanmar, 2013-2015 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - National Committee on United States-China Relations - Public Intellectuals Program (Renewal), 2008-2018 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - National Presbyterian Church - Facets of Faith Publication, 2011-2018 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    Scope and Contents
    Publication on the stained glass windows of the National Presbyterian Church.
  - New York Public Library - Ling Li Annual Fund Grant, 2009-2018 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - New York State Archives Partnership Trust - Revolutionary War Object Preservation, 2005-2018 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - New York Studio School - Digitize Lecture Program Archive, 2014-2015 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - New York University - Digital Religion Initiative, 2011-2015 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - New York University - Selected Papers of Margaret Sanger Volume Two, 2006-2018 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - New York University, School of Law - North Korea and International Law Documentary, 1996-2017 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Newark Museum - Tibetan Centennial Celebration, 2011-2018 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association - Teacher Training Workshops in China, 2004-2018 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Parrish Art Museum - "Jennifer Bartlett: After Rhapsody - A Survey of Paintings, Drawings, and Sculpture, 1977-2011" Exhibition and Catalog, 2010-2015 (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - Parrish Art Museum - Reinstall Permanent Collection in New Building, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Peabody Essex Museum - "In Plain Sight: Discovering the Furniture of Nathaniel Gould" Exhibition and Catalog, 2011-2015 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Philanthropy New York - 2014 Membership Dues, 2014-2015 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Primary Source - Curriculum Materials and Professional Development for K-12 Teachers to Increase American's Understanding of China, 2013-2015 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Princeton University - Migration, Participation, and Democratic Governance in the United States, Europe, and the Muslim World Program, 2008-2015 (Box 14, Folder 106-107)
  - Purdue University - Christianity in China Digital Project, 2011-2015 (Box 15, Folder 108-109)
  - Queens Museum of Art - "Andy Warhol's 13 Most Wanted Men and the 1964 World's Fair" Exhibition and Catalog, 2012-2015 (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art - "Gary Winogrand's America" Exhibition and Catalog, 2010-2015 (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - Shelburne Museum - Reinterpret and Reinstall American Paintings Collection, 2013-2015 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Social Science Research Council - China-Africa Relations Research Network, 2013-2018 (Box 16, Folder 113-114)
  - Society of Women Engineers - Academic Leadership for Women in Engineering Workshops, 2013-2015 (Box 16, Folder 115)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park - Exhibition and Programming Activities, 2013-2014 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - Spencer Museum of Art, University of Kansas - "Color in Ancient and Medieval East Asia" Exhibition and Research Symposium, 2012-2015 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - Henry L. Stimson Center - American Visiting Fellows to China, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - Syracuse University - Research and Training Program with North Korea's Kim Chaek University, 2002-2018 (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - Syracuse University - Delegation from North Korea's Kim Chaek University, 2009-2018 (Box 17, Folder 120)
  - Syracuse University - Travel Expenses of Presidential Delegation to North Korea (Cancelled), 2010-2018 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Teachers College, Columbia University - Open Mind On-Line Digital Archive Project, 2006-2018 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Teak Fellowship - Low-Income New York City Students Attend High School and College, 2008-2018 (Box 17, Folder 123)
  - Temple University - Scholarly Exchange Program in Comparative Religious Studies with Gagjah Mada University, Indonesia, 2004-2018 (Box 17, Folder 124-125)
  - Touchstone Theatre - Journey from the East Community-Based Project, 2014-2015 (Box 17, Folder 126)
  - Trinity University - Chinese Writers on Writing Publication, 2009-2018 (Box 18, Folder 127-128)
  - University of British Columbia - Study Tour Organized by the Canada-DPRK Knowledge Partnership Program, 2015 (Box 18, Folder 129)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara - Workshop on Religion and Leadership Training for Non-Profit, Non-Government International Organisations, 2007-2018 (Box 18, Folder 130)
  - University of Denver, Sturm College of Law - Robert B. Yegge Endowed Hispanic Scholarship Fund, 2007-2018 (Box 18, Folder 131)
  - University of Minnesota - Religion, Humanitarianism, and the World Order Program, 2006-2015 (Box 18, Folder 132-133)
  - University of Pennsylvania Museum - Reconfiguring the Silk Road: Research on East-West Exchange in Antiquity Symposium, 2010-2015 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - University of Wisconsin Foundation - Hmong Studies Initiative, 2009-2018 (Box 19, Folder 135-137)
  - University of Wisconsin-Madison - Undergraduate Scholarships for the Southeast Asian Studies Summer Institute, 2007-2015 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - Andy Warhol Museum - Reinstall and Reinterpret the Permanent Collection for the 20th Anniversary, 2014-2015 (Box 19, Folder 139)
  - WBUR Group, Boston University - On Point in China Production Initiative, 2007-2018 (Box 20, Folder 140)
  - Women in Engineering ProActive Network, Inc. (WEPAN) - Improve WEPAN Knowledge Center (WKC), 2010-2015 (Box 20, Folder 141)
  - Wings Over the Rockies Air and Space Museum - General Operations and Program Enhancements, 2006-2018 (Box 20, Folder 142)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - Southeast Asia and the Cold War: Exploring the Recent Past through Regional Archives Project, 2009-2015 (Box 20, Folder 143)
  - World Security Institute - "Islam and Muslims in the 21st Century: Challenges and Prospects" Arab Insight Journal, 2009-2018 (Box 20, Folder 144)
  - Yale-China Association - American Studies Summer Institute for Scholars from Asia, 1998-2006 (Box 20, Folder 145)
  - Yale-China Association - Terrill E. Lautz Grant, 2008-2018 (Box 20, Folder 146)
- Professorship Files, 1968-2018; 2
  - Henry R. Luce Professorship Project, 1968-2007; 1
    - Advisors 1995 Program, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 147)
    - Advisors - Craufurd D.W. Goodwin, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 148)
    - Advisors - Craufurd D.W. Goodwin - Goodwin Reports of Site Visits to Amherst, Hartford, Washington, and Lee (WordPerfect 5.1) (Box 20, Folder 148)
    - Advisors - David Campbell, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 149)
    - Advisors - David G. Campbell, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 150)
    - Advisors - Hannah H. Gray, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 151)
    - Advisors - Wei-ming Tu, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 152)
    - Conference Invites, Responses, and Travel, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 153)
    - Evaluation Correspondence, 1993-2003 (Box 21, Folder 154)
    - Future of the Henry R. Luce Professorship Program, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 155)
    - Meeting - Interdisciplinary Scholarship, Brown University, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 156)
    - Professors Salary and Total Compensation, 1968-2007 (Box 21, Folder 157)
    - Program Evaluation and Recommendations, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 158)
    - Program Status and Responses, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 159)
    - Proposals, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 160-161)
    - Proposals, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 162-165)
    - Proposals, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 166)
    - Proposed Guidelines, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 167)
    - Revised Guidelines, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 168)
    - Review Memos, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 169)
    - Site Visit Reports, 1995-2001 (Box 23, Folder 170-176)
    - "Strengthening the "Three I's" in American Higher Education: An Assessment of the Henry R. Luce Professorship Program", 1994 May (Box 24, Folder 177)
    - Symposium - Princeton, New Jersey, 1984 May 13-15 (Box 24, Folder 178-179)
    - Symposium - Tarrytown, New York, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 180)
    - Symposium - New York, New York, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 181)
    - Symposium - New York, New York, 2004 May 7 (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - Professorship Files, 1989-2018; 2
    Each university/college's file contains proposals, professor information, site visits, correspondence, annual reports, and grant payment/acknoledgement/extension letters.
    - Amherst College - Emerging Democracies and the Rule of Law, 1995-2004 (Box 25, Folder 183)
    - Bard College - Human Rights, Democracy, and New Media, 2001-2014 (Box 25, Folder 184-186)
    - Barnard College - Migration and Social Order, 1992-2005 (Box 25, Folder 187-188)
    - Boston College - Nursing Ethics, 1993-2002 (Box 26, Folder 189-190)
    - Carleton College - Human Dimensions of Global Change, 1995-2005 (Box 26, Folder 191-192)
    - George Washington University - Human Origins, 2002-2006 (Box 26, Folder 193-195)
    - Georgetown University - International Relations and Information Age Technology, 2000-2010 (Box 27, Folder 196-197)
    - Gettysburg College - The Civil War Era, 1997-2007 (Box 27, Folder 198-199)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Bioethics and Moral and Political Theory, 2005-2011 (Box 28, Folder 200-202)
    - Kalamazoo College - Global Technological Innovation, 2000-2014 (Box 28, Folder 203-204)
    - Oberlin College - The Emerging Arts, 2000-2009 (Box 29, Folder 205-206)
    - Occidental College - Urban Environmental Studies, 1996-2008 (Box 29, Folder 207-209)
    - Pitzer College - Brain, Mind, and Medicine: Cross-Cultural Perspectives, 1996-2005 (Box 30, Folder 210-211)
    - Princeton University - Intelligent Systems and Human Reasoning, 2000-2013 (Box 30, Folder 212-215)
    - Trinity College - Health and Human Rights, 1999-2006 (Box 31, Folder 216)
    - Tufts University - Science and Humanitarian Studies, 1999-2014 (Box 31, Folder 217-218)
    - University of Denver - Conflict Resolution, 1998-2014 (Box 32, Folder 219-222)
    - University of Miami - Family and Community, 1996-2004 (Box 32, Folder 223-224)
    - University of Notre Dame - Religion, Conflict, and Peacebuilding, 1999-20118 (Box 33, Folder 225-228)
    - Washington University, St. Louis - Collective and Individual Memory, 1998-2008 (Box 33, Folder 229-230)
    - Wellesley College - Biology, Ethics, and the Politics of Human Reproduction, 1992-2001 (Box 34, Folder 231-232)
    - Yale University - Social Thought and Ethics, 1989-2005 (Box 34, Folder 233)
- United States-China Cooperative Research Program, 1988-2010; 3
  The United States-China Cooperative Research Program was initiated in 1998. It's aim was to encourage sustained joint research by American and Chinese scholars on significant topics in the humanities and social sciences to improve understanding of China and US-China relations. The cooperative research projects typically involved two or more collaborators on both the Chinese and American sides, working together over a three-year period.
  - University of California, Berkeley - Handbook on Classical Chinese Literature, 1998-2010 (Box 34, Folder 234-235)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Cultural Antecedents and Origins of Chinese Civilizations, 1998-2003 (Box 35, Folder 236-237)
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Landscape Archaeology and Ancient Salt Production in Zhong Xian, Chongqing Municipality, China, 1998-2010 (Box 35, Folder 238)
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Socal Stratification in China in a Period of Transition, 1994-2010 (Box 35, Folder 239)
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Local Archives and Court Records - Social Change and Law, 1989-2004 (Box 35, Folder 240)
  - University of California, San Diego - Civil Society in China, 1991-2004 (Box 36, Folder 241)
  - University of California, Santa Cruz - A Cultural History of Women and Work in Twentieth-Century China, 1995-2010 (Box 36, Folder 242)
  - University of Chicago - Between Han and Tang: Art and Archaeology in a Transitional Period, 1998-2004 (Box 36, Folder 243)
  - University of Chicago - Chinese Urban and Rural Family Life, 1992-1997 (Box 36, Folder 244)
  - University of Chicago - China after the Cultural Revolution, 1988-2010 (Box 36, Folder 245)
  - University of Maryland, College Park - Art of Shanghai, 1850-1930, 1994-2007 (Box 37, Folder 246-247)
  - University of Massachusetts, Amherst - People and Environment on the Northern Chinese Frontiers, 1998-2010 (Box 37, Folder 248)
  - University of Michigan - Survey Research on Chinese Family Dynamics, 1989-2003 (Box 37, Folder 249)
  - University of Michigan - Structures and Outcomes in Chinese Culture, 1988-1997 (Box 37, Folder 250-251)
  - University of Minnesota, Duluth - Anyang Project: Co-Evolution of Human Societies, 1997-2002 (Box 38, Folder 252-254)
  - University of Minnesota, Twin Cities - Urban Consumers and Material Culture in China, 1996-2001 (Box 38, Folder 255)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Economic and Social Change in China, 1996-2010 (Box 38, Folder 256)
  - University of Oregon - Mapping the Book Trade: Print Culture in Late Imperial China, 1998-2007 (Box 39, Folder 257-258)
  - University of Pennsylvania - The Ancient Desiccated Corpses of Xinjiang, 1994-2010 (Box 39, Folder 259)